I left a suitcase on the train to London the other day.
几天前我把一只手提箱忘在开往伦敦的火车上了.
Can you describe it, sir?
先生,您能描述一下它吗?
It's a small blue case and it's got a zip.
是只蓝色的小箱子,上面有拉链.
There's a label on the handle with my name and address on it.
箱把上有一个标签,上面写着我的姓名和住址.
Is this case yours?
这箱子是您的吗?
No, that's not mine.
不,那不是我的.
What about this one?
这只是不是?
This one's got a label.
这只箱子有张标签.
Let me see it.
让我看看.
What's your name and address?
您的姓名和住址?
David Hall,83,Bridge Street.
David Hall,大桥路83号.
That's right. D.N. Hall, 83, Bridge Street.
那就对了.D.N.Hall,大桥路83号.
Three pounds fifty pence,please.
请付3英镑50便士.
Here you are.
给你.
Thank you.
谢谢您.
Hey!
嗨!
What's the matter?
怎么回事?
This case doesn't belong to me!
这箱子不是我的!
You've given me the wrong case!
你给错了!